<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Main Page on Fatih Doğan</title><link>https://fatihdgn.com/en/</link><description>Recent content in Main Page on Fatih Doğan</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Fatih Doğan.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fatihdgn.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Development on an Ancient Windows Mobile Phone</title><link>https://fatihdgn.com/en/blog/development-on-an-ancient-windows-mobile-phone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fatihdgn.com/en/blog/development-on-an-ancient-windows-mobile-phone/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had this Crea MS2 phone that&amp;rsquo;s been lying around for a while. One boring afternoon and I started to think that maybe I can do something with it. I&amp;rsquo;ve actually used it way back then and I was excited to see a phone that can run fully fledged Windows, but yeah, I&amp;rsquo;ve had my hopes up too much because I quickly realized it was running a mobile version of it.</description></item><item><title>Meta</title><link>https://fatihdgn.com/en/blog/meta/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fatihdgn.com/en/blog/meta/</guid><description>Note: This is my first English post. Well, technically this is the second one but the first one is in my Turkish blog and I added multi-language support to my site yesterday, so&amp;hellip;
I want to talk about meta and I want to talk about talking about it. It&amp;rsquo;s strange that we are not talking meta ABOUT meta, like it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have it.
Not to deep dive in, let&amp;rsquo;s start with the definition of meta; (of a creative work) referring to itself or to the conventions of its genre; self-referential.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://fatihdgn.com/en/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fatihdgn.com/en/projects/</guid><description>Projects Throughout my life, I have developed and been involved in numerous projects of various sizes. Below is a reverse chronological list of some of them that come to mind. This list is, of course, currently incomplete. I will add future projects here as time allows.
VavaCars A platform for buying and selling used cars. I contributed to various features and changes ranging from the ordering process to displaying vehicle details and relevant legal documents.</description></item></channel></rss>